<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text</string>
    <string name="article_title">Beatles Time Capsule</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">Favorite Fab Four Facts</string>
    <string name="article_text"><b>As a boy, John Lennon had to choose between mom and dad.</b>
        \n\n
        <b>www.rockument.com</b>
        \n\n
        This heartbreaking story has been repeated in various biographies and books about the Beatles. John’s father, Alfred “Freddy” Lennon, worked as a seaman and was not home in the first five years of his life. When he came back, he took 5-year-old John with him on a short holiday, and then wouldn’t return him to his home in Liverpool (in an area known as Merseyside).
\n\n
When his mother, Julia, came to get John, Freddy asked John if he wanted to sail away to seek his fortune with his father. Of course John said yes. Fighting back tears, Julia said goodbye and left John with Freddy.
\n\n
In a few minutes it dawned on John that Julia was leaving forever, and he raced out of the holiday cottage and ran down the street to catch his mother! He stayed for a while with Julia, but eventually Julia left him with her sister Mimi and her husband George, who raised him. John lived with Aunt Mimi until his late teens, when he went off to Hamburg with the other Beatles.
\n\n
        <i>Paul knows “20 Flight Rock” and shows John how to tune a guitar.</i>
\n\n
When Paul McCartney first met John, John was the leader of the Quarrymen on one of his first gigs. The Quarrymen were a skiffle group, inspired by skiffle tunes such as “Rock Island Line” by Lonnie Donnegan. Paul met John after the gig and showed him how to tune his guitar, then played Eddie Cochran’s “20 Flight Rock” flawlessly. For an example, first listen to Eddie Cochran’s original version, and then Paul McCartney’s CHOBA B CCCP (Back in the USSR).
\n\n
This impressed John. For a while John agonized over whether to ask someone so much more musically competent than he was to join his band, but realized eventually that the band itself mattered more. John and Paul would eventually form one of the most famous songwriting partnerships in popular music, and become the most influential composers in rock and roll.
\n\n\
</string>
</resources>
